blogcheer.com 2015-05-11

# Privacy Policy - How to Blog - Best Blogging Tips

By using [**Blogcheer**](http://blogcheer.com/ "How to blog and Best Blogging Tips").com you agree to our terms and conditions and privacy policy of this website. Blogcheer terms and conditions apply to all the users who visit our website and if you don’t agree to our terms and condition, then kindly don’t visit the website. Blogcheer respect your privacy and will not use your personal information with anyone. Blogcheer has created this privacy policy in order to demonstrate our determination to your privacy policy.

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information when you register to our website. Users may be asked to enter their name, address, website and some other information like telephone number etc.  We won’t share your personal information like name, address, and email with any third party which is not related with Blogcheer.

#### What do we use your information for?

We use your information for contacting you if required. Other than that, we use your information to enhance your experience and to improve our website.

#### Do we use cookies?

Yes, we use cookies to count return visits to our website, for enabling automatic logins, for personalizing the site and to deliver interest based content. For monitoring traffic on our website.

**Do we show third party[advertisement](http://blogcheer.com/advertisement/)?**

Yes, we display some paid advertisement on our website which may take you to some other website or any external source. [Google](http://blogcheer.com/category/google/) as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads. Google’s use of DART cookies enable it to serve ads, based on their visit to your website and other sites on the internet. We are not responsible for the content of the external website.

**Do we use Third Party Links?**

Yes, we do use third party links, the links maybe paid or we use other links for providing extra information.

Information to any third party/company:

No, we won’t share your personal information to any third party or company. Your information won’t be shared with any party.

Children Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

We are in compliance with the requirement of “Children Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)” and won’t collect any data from anyone under the age of 13 years.

Do we display Adult content:  
No, we won’t display any adult content on our website. We respect our users and we won’t show such content.

Do we promote gambling?

No we won’t promote gambling, poker on our website.

Changes in the privacy policy:

If we want to change our privacy policy we will change it here.
